(Howard:)20 minutes in,
they find a prune pit.
(Raj:)Actually, how do you feel about
watching House of 1000 Corpses?
(Howard:)A straight-up gore-fest?
You hate this stuff.
(Raj:)I do, but for some reason,
Emily loves it
(Raj:)and wants to watch it
with me tomorrow,
(Raj:)so I thought if
I saw it with you first,
(Raj:)then I could act cool
about it with her.
(Howard:)That's actually not a bad plan.
(Howard:)I can sit through
the colonoscopy now,
(Howard:)but that first time I was like,
"Oh, my God, a prune pit!"
-So you'd watch it?
-Sure.
(Raj:)You're a good friend.
I owe you one.
Howard!
Help me get out of the tub!
(Raj:)Not that one.
(Sheldon:)So we're just randomly
choosing a restaurant
(Sheldon:)-without researching it online?
-Yep.
(Leonard:)Great.
(Sheldon:)This is how Anything Can
Happen Thursday turns